http://www.2d3.com/privacy-policy

Effective November 26, 2018
Insitu, Inc. (“Insitu”) is a Washington corporation and a wholly owned subsidiary of The Boeing Company. This Insitu Website Privacy Statement (“Privacy Statement”) describes how Insitu collects, uses, shares and otherwise processes information relating to individuals (“Personal Data”). Insitu is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you an efficient and safe online experience. Please read this Privacy Statement carefully to learn about your rights and choices regarding Insitu’s privacy practices.
This Privacy Statement applies to the Insitu websites and governs data collection and usage. A reference to “Insitu,” “we,” “us” or the “Company” is a reference to Insitu, Inc.
COLLECTION OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA
Personal Data is the information that you provide to Insitu which personally identifies you, such as your name, email address, or billing information, or other data that can be reasonably linked to such information by Insitu. Insitu may also collect anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, or preferences and interests as they relate to Insitu products and technology.
Additionally, there may be information about your computer hardware and software that is collected by Insitu. This information can include: anonymized IP addresses, browser type, domain names, access times, websites visited and referring website addresses. Insitu may use web server logs to collect data for metrics purposes. This information is used by Insitu for our website operations, to maintain quality of website services, to customize the content and/or layout of webpages for each visitor and to provide general statistics regarding website use. Insitu does not provide this anonymized data to third parties.
Insitu will provide you with access to your Personal Data that we hold for any purpose within practical and legal limits. This includes requests that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if Insitu is not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. Access, correction, or deletion requests can be made by emailing us at WebsitePrivacy@insitu.com.
Insitu encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Insitu so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Insitu is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Insitu and Insitu family of websites.
USE OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA
Insitu collects information to provide better services to all of our users. Insitu uses that information, including Personal Data, to operate the Insitu websites and to deliver the products and services you have requested. Additionally, Insitu may use your Personal Data to inform you, as permitted by law and subject to your contact preferences, of other products or services available from Insitu and its affiliates or to contact you to conduct research about your opinion of current and future Insitu products and services. Although we hope you will find our promotional communications interesting, you may opt out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each message.
Insitu does not sell, rent or lease its customer data to third parties. Insitu may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your Personal Data is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Insitu may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Insitu, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
Insitu may disclose Personal Data, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on Insitu; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Insitu; and/or, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect personal safety.
USE OF COOKIES
Insitu websites may utilize “cookies” to help you customize your online experience. A cookie is a small file that is stored on your computer by a web page server.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to save you time. A cookie tells the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Insitu pages, or register with Insitu websites or services, a cookie helps the Insitu webpage to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of re-recording Personal Data. When you return to the same Insitu websites, the information you previously provided can be retrieved so you can easily use the Insitu features that you customized.
Additionally, cookies may be used to track the websites and pages you have visited within Insitu’s websites to determine which Insitu products and services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising to customers whose behaviors indicate that they are interested in a particular subject area. In some instances, Insitu may use tracking cookies that recognize a unique identifier from a cookie placed on your device by another website. These are used by Insitu to gauge the success of our marketing campaigns and to optimize your future experience on our website. For instance, we may use a tracking script to determine whether you visit our product pages after visiting a magazine website where we placed a digital ad.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. You can usually modify your browser setting to instruct it to accept or decline cookies. However, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Insitu services or websites you visit.
COLLECTION AND USE OF LOCATION DATA
When you use Insitu websites, we may collect and process information about the proximity of your physical location. We use various technologies to determine location, such as IP address or GPS, which may, provide information on nearby devices, Wi-Fi access points or cell towers. Location data is used and disclosed in accordance with the “Use of Your Personal Data” section above.
SECURITY OF INFORMATION
While a user’s general interaction with Insitu websites (e.g., submission of suggestions) is not considered confidential, Insitu does secure Personal Data on Insitu computer servers in a controlled, secure environment. Personal Data is protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. If and when Personal Data is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
Insitu does not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personal Data from children under 13 years of age. If you believe that we have collected Personal Data from a child under the age of 13 years, please inform us by email at WebsitePrivacy@insitu.com so that we may delete the information.
DATA TRANSMITTED INTERNATIONALLY
If you are utilizing our website from a location outside of the United States, Insitu realizes that you may want to know whether your personal information will be transferred out of your country of origin. Please be aware that when you register or request a transaction on our websites, your Personal Data may be transferred to computers in the United States or any other country where Insitu or its affiliates, subsidiaries or service providers maintain facilities. We take steps to ensure that the data we collect under this Policy is processed according to the provisions of this Privacy Statement and the requirements of applicable law wherever the data is located.
REORGANIZATION OF INSITU
In the event of a reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer, or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock, Insitu may be required to disclose Personal Data to the new owners, subject to a requirement that such information be used only in accordance with this Privacy Statement.
CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT
Insitu will occasionally update this Privacy Statement to reflect company and customer feedback. Insitu encourages you to periodically review the Privacy Statement because users of our websites will be prospectively bound by the then-current version.
CONTACT INFORMATION
Insitu welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Statement. If you believe that Insitu has not adhered to the terms set forth in this Privacy Statement, please contact Insitu at WebsitePrivacy@insitu.com.
For Insitu Pacific’s Privacy Policy, download the PDF:
2018 INSITU. All Rights Reserved.
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Software Support Ticket
Sales Inquiry
